# SHOON LEI PHYU (REI)

### **Profile**

Hardworking, ambitious, and result-oriented team-player, LLB and Business Information Technology graduate with 3 years plus working experience in digital transformation, IT consulting, IT assets management, network supervising, IT problem-solving, web application development with javascript, project managing, and project evaluation.

### **Experience**

### 01/5/2021 -Present

### **Digital Solutions Executive**

Prudential Myanmar Company Ltd, Yangon - UI/UX designing of proposed projects and

systems

- solving technical problems for enterprise mobile applications

- strategic planning on customer engagement initiatives from technical perspectives.

- support in creating enterprise web applications

- suggest the UI/UX designs for a smooth user experience

\_

# 22/6/2020 **-** 30/4/2021

### **Project Coordinator - Digital Business**

Prudential Myanmar Company Ltd , Yangon

- Legal review and advise on legal partnerships
- Building internal office applications using PowerApps and PowerBI
- Coordinate with Senior Manager to meet the IT project requirements.
- handles Digital Marketing Projects
- ensure that the Digital Marketing reaches its target.
- negotiating budget with the partners.
- advise on digital trends
- plan marketing activities

### 1/4/2019 -28/22020

#### **IT Associate**

Forval Myanmar Co. Ltd., Yangon, Myanmar

- Develop Kintone Web applications using JavaScript, Node JS, Kintone REST API;
- Assist with complex technical projects;
- Go to Customer Sites and Client followups;
- IT Consulting;
- Supervise the company network;
- Researches and recommends system equipment upgrades and manages IT assets;
- Performs routine security checks on the system;

### Skills IT Skill Project Management Excel Kintone Web application JavaScript HTML **CSS** MvSOL PHP Networking IT Security Tableau Microsoft 36 Legal Skill Commercial Laws Intellectual Property Consulting IT legal contracts Language English Japanese

### Contact

- ★ Yangon
- **a** +95 9 43035285
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/shoonleiphyu/

1/10/2018 - 21/12/2018	<ul> <li>Project Coordinator Intern</li> <li>Opto Ai Co. Ltd (Refre), Osaka, Japan</li> <li>data analysis on old people's health care data of Myanmar</li> <li>planning for the Japanese Language Teaching Curriculum for Myanmar citizens;</li> <li>public demonstration and presentations about the project;</li> </ul>
1/2/2018 - 31/1/2019	<b>Burmese and English Language Tutor MMTutor</b> , Yangon, Myanmar teaching Foreigners the Burmese and English Language.
1/5/2015 - 30/9/2018	<ul> <li>Data Clerk and Finance Assistant</li> <li>PACE - people's alliance for credible elections, Yangon, Myanmar</li> <li>handling problems at the call center in the national election days</li> <li>input the surveyed data into the database system and check data input error;</li> <li>calculating the payroll using Spreadsheets and Microsoft Excel</li> </ul>
Education	
2018 - 2020	Masters of Laws (LLM) in Commercial University of Yangon, Yangon, Myanmar
	<i>y y y y</i>
9/2019 - 3/202 0	Certificate of Achievement for Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) VCE Training, Yangon
	2 Certificate of Achievement for Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA)
0	2 Certificate of Achievement for Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) VCE Training, Yangon B.Sc (Hons) in Business Information Technology
0 2013 - 2018	2 Certificate of Achievement for Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) VCE Training, Yangon  B.Sc (Hons) in Business Information Technology University of Greenwich, London (UK)  Diploma in Project Management Institute of Commercial Management, Unit
0 2013 - 2018 2019 - 2019	2 Certificate of Achievement for Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) VCE Training, Yangon  B.Sc (Hons) in Business Information Technology University of Greenwich, London (UK)  Diploma in Project Management Institute of Commercial Management, Unit ed Kingdom  Bachelor of Laws (LLB)
0 2013 - 2018 2019 - 2019 2013 - 2018	2 Certificate of Achievement for Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) VCE Training, Yangon  B.Sc (Hons) in Business Information Technology University of Greenwich, London (UK)  Diploma in Project Management Institute of Commercial Management, Unit ed Kingdom  Bachelor of Laws (LLB) University of Yangon, Yangon  Certificate of Achievement for "Lecture Series on 5S/Kaizen and Management"

### <u>Interests</u>

- Playing Basketball
- Reading
- Learning new things

## Achievements

- Extra Effort Award 2020 in Prudential
  - Participated in
- Business Plan Competition at SFU
  - Distinction A in Project
- Management Exam, ICM UK.
- Professional Sales Training
  - Participated in 2018
- ASEAN University Game as Myanmar Basketball Player

### **Projects**

2018 <b>POINT OF SALES SYSTEM OF NGWE WATHONE CO. LTD</b>
---

2019-2020 KINTONE APPLICATION SYSTEM FOR VARIOUS COMPANIES

2021 **CHA-CHING E-LEARNING PLATFORM** 

2021 **UI/UX DESIGN OF INSURANCE PRODUCTS** 

### **Publications**

#### Term Paper

### **FOREIGN INVESTMENT IN MYANMAR 2018**

Shoon Lei Phyu | 2018

the insights of the foreign investments in Myanmar and how to apply the legal guidelines.

#### Dissertation

### LEGAL PROTECTION OF UTILITY MODEL IN MYANMAR AND JAPAN

Shoon Lei Phyu | 2021

The protection on Utility Model in legal perspective and the exercise of legal protection on Intellectual Property in Japan and Myanmar.

### Volunteer work

#### **FOUNDER AND DPO**

ProLab Myanmar | 2020 - Present

Aiming to promote the Myanmar Sports Era becomes popular again with digitalization.

